Mr. Wei.
魏先生
Welcome.
您来了
This way, please.
请
This is the Shanghai site
这就是上海站
of the French Concession Intelligence Team.
法租界情报组的工作点
From now on,
以后您就是
you're part of the intelligence team,
情报组的组员
with your guise
对外身份
being an employee at the AG Brewery.
是安琪啤酒公司的职员
Right this way.
里面请
Mr. Wei, this way.
魏先生请
This is the office Mr. Yu
这里是愚先生
has prepared
特意给魏先生
specially for you.
准备的办公室
And this,
这个
is a car for you.
是给您准备的车
If you have
如果您还有什么
any other requirements,
其他别的需求
just let me know,
随时跟我讲
and I'll look after your needs.
我来解决
I'll report
您的调查结果
your findings to Mr. Yu.
也由我向愚先生汇报
All this...
我
for me, alone?
都我一个人用
Exactly.
没错
Mr. Yu is the boss,
愚先生是老板
you, can I say,
那我能理解
are
您是愚先生
my assistant assigned by him?
配给我的助手吗
Absolutely.
当然是
Tell me,
说
who is Hua Zhen
华桢现在
currently in contact with?
跟什么人在联络
A journalist named Peng Ganwen.
一个叫做彭甘文的记者
Peng Ganwen,
彭甘文
from what I know,
据我所知
has offended the police.
这个人得罪了警察
Hua Zhen
华桢
rescued his wife
从警察手里
from the police
救出了他的太太
and afterwards, she disappeared,
之后这个女人就消失了
likely
很有可能
hidden by Hua Zhen for her protection.
是被华桢藏起来保护了
Where is Hua Zhen now?
华桢现在在哪里
At Jiangnan Shipyard.
江南造船所
He's here in Shanghai
他这次来上海
officially
名义上
on a mission
是执行电雷学校的
of the S.M.C..
任务的
Tell me more about this Peng Ganwen.
那说说这个彭甘文吧
He's a journalist for Shenbao Newspaper,
他是《申报》的记者
and also a member of the NSO.
也是救国会的委员
As far as I know,
据我所知这个人
he's a pro-Communist.
属于亲共分子
Hua Zhen's rescue of his wife
这次华桢救了他的太太
might have been
不知道是不是
under communist directives.
受共产党的指使
How did he manage to cross the police?
这个人怎么得罪警察了
He uncovered some
他知道了一些
internal scandals within the Public Security Bureau
公安局内部的丑闻
and planned to expose them.
想要公布出去
I see,
行了
he's really stirred up trouble.
看来他惹的麻烦太大了
Mr. Jin,
金先生
take a look at this.
看看这个吧
These are
这是我积攒的
all the materials I've collected
所有有关救国会的材料
on the NSO.
都在这里了
There have been
所谓
active communists
全国各界救国联合会
in the so-called national salvation organization
早就有共产党
for quite a while.
在里面活动了
Back when I
我当时在
was at the Shanghai Garrison Command,
淞沪警备司令部的时候
I didn't want to alert them,
没有惊动他们
planning to let more fish flow in
是为了把池塘养大一点
and allow the fish to multiply.
鱼养多一点
Now,
好了
Hua Zhen's involvement
现在华桢
has given us a chance.
跟他们有瓜葛了
He's saved NSO member,
他救了救国会的人
and NSO has to respond.
救国会就不得不有反应
Once the NSO responds,
救国会一有反应
our opportunity has come.
我们的机会就来了
Hua Zhen saved Mrs. Peng.
华桢救了彭太太
If you save someone, you have to offer shelter.
救了人 人就得安置
Hotels and guesthouses
什么酒店啊客栈
are entirely out of the question.
完全不可能
They're too risky.
太容易暴露了
That's why
所以
I know of
我知道
a few houses here,
在这里有这么几个据点
possible places they use
是他们落脚点
as shelters,
也就是安全屋
like
比如说华界的
Zhejiang-Ningbo Association,
浙宁会馆
Merchant Shipping Hall,
商船会馆
and three stand-alone apartments
还有法租界的
in the French Concession
三栋独立的公寓房
in which they've been
一直有他们
renting rooms for long.
长期租的房间
Shanghai is not big.
上海就这么大
If we keep watching
我们派人盯着
and search one by one,
一间一间地查
we'll find them eventually.
迟早一定会有结果
These people outside,
外面这些人
from the Special Service?
特务处的
Can you mobilize them?
你能调动得了吗
Everyone in the Special Service
特务处里所有的人
is at your disposal.
听候魏先生差遣
How much to fill in?
加多少油
Fill it up, thanks.
加满 谢谢
Got it.
好
Here you are.
师傅 给
Okay, thank you.
好嘞 谢谢
Excuse me,
师傅
I was wondering
我想知道一下
if you know of any truck drivers around here.
这附近有没有开货车的
Oh yes,
有啊
they often
还经常
come here to refuel.
来我们这里加油啊
Why?
怎么了
I run an insurance company
我是开保险公司的
and I'm interested
我想知道
in finding out if these truck drivers
这些货车司机愿不愿意
would be interested in insuring their trucks.
给自己的车买保险
Asking them one by one
但是一家一家问
might annoy them,
我怕他们嫌我烦
so I thought I'd ask for your guidance first.
那我想请您指点一下
You've come to the right person.
你算问对人了
This is
这附近
the only gas station in this area,
只有我们这一家加油站
and all the trucks
这条街上的车
on this street come here.
都得来我们这里加油的
I know of
我知道
only three companies that own trucks around here:
只有三家有货车的
a post office,
一家邮局
a trading company,
一家贸易公司
and a
前面那边
seafood seller right down the street.
还有一家卖水产的
They come here the most.
最常来
You might want to check over there.
你可以到前面去看看
Great, thanks.
好 谢谢你
You're welcome.
不客气
Hongyang, hurry up, let's go.
鸿杨 快点 走了
Come on.
快点儿
Coming, I'm coming.
来了来了
Let's go
走
Wenxiang,
文祥
hurry, let's go.
快点儿 走了走了
Let's go drink.
喝酒去
Move it, quickly!
走走走 快快快
Mengling, time to go.
梦玲 走了
Goodbye.
再见
Did you get all the locations?
地点都记住了吗
Got them.
记住了
Tonight I'll go there
晚上我跟向远生
with Xiang Yuansheng.
一块儿过去
I hope your cooperation goes smoothly.
那希望你们合作顺利
Don't forget your mission.
别忘了你的任务
How could I?
怎么可能
By the way,
对了
someone from the Fourth Station got hurt.
四所有人受伤
They wanted me to visit.
想让我去看一看
Forget it,
算了
I won't go.
还是不去了
I wouldn't be of any help anyway.
去了也帮不上什么忙
Goodbye.
再见
What did I say?
我说什么来着
I told you the Captain wouldn't be home,
我就说队长不在家吧
and you didn't believe me.
还不信
He's not here.
不在
I just wonder
我就纳闷了
what's so busy with
天天在冯广云手底下
working under Feng Guangyun
有什么可忙的
that he doesn't even have time to visit Dongbao.
去看冬宝都没时间
Has anyone seen him recently?
你们最近有人见过他吗
Yuansheng,
远生
you're rarely back.
你好不容易回来一次
The Captain should at least meet you.
队长总该见你一面吧
Not yet.
还没有
Alright.
行了行了
enough complaining.
别抱怨了
Let's go.
走吧
The lad,
这小子
thirty years old,
三十了
stuck in the Fourth Station for years,
在四所窝了这么多年
finally made it to the precinct.
好不容易荣升到分局了
He'd been through a lot.
不容易
I introduced him
以前给他介绍
many good jobs,
多少好差事
but he never took them.
他就是不去
Those jobs were well paid ones,
哪个不比四所挣得多
but he was set on being a cop.
一门心思就想当个警察
Besides,
再说了
he's now under Feng's roof.
人在屋檐下
He never got along
以前就跟冯科长
with Feng before.
他就不对付
Now he must impress Feng
他不是也得好好努努力
with hardworking and good performance.
表现表现
Am I right?
是吧
It's understandable...
这都可以理解
Captain?
队长
Capt... Captain,
队 队长
we just visited Dongbao.
大家刚看完冬宝
We collected some money for him
我们凑了点儿钱
to buy some good food
让冬宝买点儿好吃的
for his health.
补一补
He's optimistic.
他这个人乐观得很
Don't worry about him.
不用担心他
Good that you visited him.
你们看了就好
I've told Erbai before,
之前我跟二白说过了
I've been too busy
我最近比较忙
to visit him.
没时间去看他
What about you?
我们看
Do you even treat us like crew members?
你还把我们当队员吗
Competing for Feng's mercy
每天跟冯广云手底下
against his lackeys every day,
那帮小喽啰比忠诚
and couldn't spare two more minutes
冬宝结婚
in Dongbao's wedding.
你坐两分钟就走
I just want to know,
我就想问问你
is your Criminal Investigation Dept. really that busy,
刑警队是真的忙啊
or do you
还是你压根
just not want to see us?
就不想见我们
That's enough!
少说两句
This is my share.
把我那份也算上
Let him buy something good.
让他买点好吃的
Give it back to him!
还给他
Dongbao doesn't need your money!
冬宝是缺你这点儿钱吗
Let's go.
走
Hold on!
等一下
I'll make sure
这钱
Dongbao gets this money.
我帮你给冬宝
Don't let him off the hook!
不能便宜了他
There are three trunk owners
这条路一共有三个地方
in this neighborhood.
有货车
First, the post office,
第一个是邮局
second, a trading company,
第二个是贸易公司
and third, a seafood company.
第三个水产品公司
The first two got the wrong trunks.
前两个货车的样式不对
So, it's just this
现在就剩下
San Yang Fisheries.
这个三洋水产公司了
We'll make our move
等那两个人走了
right after those two leave.
我们想办法进去
It's the right type.
就是这种货车的样式
Look at the wear trace
你看这个螺丝的
on this screw.
磨损程度
It seems like the license plate
这个车牌
has been frequently removed and reattached.
应该经常取了又挂
9521?
九五二一
On the night
那天晚上
when you and Luo Minmin
你跟骆珉敏
took away Mrs. Peng,
要带走彭太太之前
I saw a truck
我看见从后面
chase after you.
追过来一辆货车
I knocked down some poles
是我推倒了杆子
to block its way.
挡了一下
When the poles fell,
那些杆子倒下来的时候
they hit the front of the truck.
砸在了车头上面
See these scratches.
你看这些划痕
Come on,
走
let's get inside.
进去看看
How come
这里怎么
there's no one on duty?
连一个值班的人都没有
It's 7:30 PM.
现在是七点半
Maybe they
会不会是
have less inventory?
水产公司点货的少啊
Either their business is poor,
要么是他们生意不好
or
要么
this place
这里就是
is purely an assembly place for them.
他们的一个窝点
Let's go.
走吧
Damn the water pipe's broken again.
破水管又坏了
Never give me peace of mind.
天天的
When I was on the Meng murder case,
查孟家凶杀案的时候
I suspected
我就怀疑
that Feng Guangyun
冯广云在外面
hired a group of thugs on the outside
豢养了一批打手
to handle dirty work for him
专门帮他处理
that the police couldn't openly
警察不方便出面的
deal with.
脏事儿
Mr. Peng was also
彭记者也是
taken by that truck.
被那辆车抓走的
No one saw it happen.
没有人亲眼所见
Now, it's just speculation.
只是推测
Because the precinct's records
因为分局的档案袋里
indicate that Mr. Peng was secretly arrested
彭记者是被冯广云
by Feng Guangyun.
秘密逮捕的
I've looked everywhere possible,
我找了所有能找的地方
prisons, detention centers,
监狱 看守所
and couldn't find Mr. Peng.
都找不到彭记者
I suspect
我怀疑彭记者
he's been secretly detained
就是被这帮人抓了
by these thugs.
秘密关了起来
Mrs. Peng also mentioned that a truck
彭太太确实也提过
without license plates
彭记者失踪前两天
was lurking around
他家附近
near her house
确实出现过
a couple of days before Mr. Peng disappeared.
一辆无牌货车
Without any other leads,
现在没有别的线索
we have to start with this truck.
只能从这辆车下手
Fortunately, we now know
好在我们现在知道
its license number.
这辆车的车牌号
Tomorrow I'll try my luck
明天我去分局档案室
in the precinct's archives.
碰碰运气
I don't have many thick jackets.
我厚衣服没那么多
Make do for now.
你先将就将就
I'll find some more
回头我再找
for you later.
找给你
It's fine,
没事儿
as long as I can wear it.
能穿就行
On a closer look,
仔细一看
it's alright.
还行
Your clothes,
你的衣服
it's up to you.
你说可以就可以
Let's go,
走吧
my treat today.
今天我请
I forgot,
我忘了
last time at Dongbao's place,
那天去冬宝家
I gave him all my money.
我把钱掏空了
Typical.
习惯了
When have you ever paid the bill
哪次出来跟你吃面
when we go out for noodles?
你掏过钱
I didn't expect it.
没指望
Boss.
老板
Stop looking.
别找了
Yours is empty too.
你的也被我掏空了
Eat noodles without money?
不带钱就敢过来吃面啊
Three bowls of Yangchun noodles.
三碗阳春面
Thanks, boss.
谢谢老板
Coming right up.
马上来
I have money. It's on me.
我有钱 我请客
Join me.
过来吧
Captain,
队长
I've given
那些钱
the money to Yu.
我已经交给小玉了
She asked me to thank you.
她让我跟你说声谢谢
Now I have a few questions.
现在我问你们几个问题
Go ahead.
说
Have you guys
你们是不是
been working together all along?
早就在一起做事了
You are investigating
你们在一起查
Mr. Peng's case,
彭记者的案子
right?
对不对
I was there
之前在医院
for everything that happened
发生的所有的事情
at the hospital,
我都在场
and you still kept it from me.
你们居然还瞒着我
We were indeed investigating
我们确实在查
Mr. Peng's case.
彭记者的案子
Captain,
队长
Mrs. Peng's case
之前彭太太来报案
was the last one
是我接的警
I took
也是我在四所
at the Fourth Station.
接的最后一个警
You told me
那个时候你就说
to stop looking into it,
让我别再管了
but since
但我既然已经
I'm already involved,
牵扯进来了
let me in.
就让我跟你们一起吧
Minmin,
珉敏
it's too...
这件事情
I know what you're going to say.
我知道你要说什么
Even though I'm no longer
虽然我现在已经
a police officer,
不是警察了
I feel like
但是我始终觉得
I haven't completed
我在四所的
my last case at the Fourth Station.
最后一个案子没有办完
You're a police officer too,
你是警察
you must understand my feeling,
你一定明白这种感觉
right?
对不对
I can stop asking
你们不说的
questions.
我可以不问
But if there's anything
但是要是有什么
I can help with,
我能帮得上忙的地方
please tell me.
一定要告诉我好吗
I hope the month I spent
我希望在四所的
at the Fourth Station
这一个月
can have a clear end.
可以有始有终
Okay,
行吗
Captain?
队长
Understood.
知道了
Here are the noodles.
面来了
Take your time.
三位慢点吃
Let's eat.
吃面吧
Thanks, boss.
谢谢老板
Eat up,
多吃点儿
and if it's not enough,
要是不够吃的话
we can order more.
还可以再要
Wait,
等一下
it was you
队长的钱包
who emptied the Captain's wallet, right?
是你掏空的吧
You knew everything.
你明明什么都知道
Why did you echo Erbai?
为什么还要跟二白起哄
And you, Captain,
队长还有你
you care so much about the Fourth Station,
你明明那么关心四所
why argue with Erbai?
为什么还要跟二白吵
Couldn't you just humor him?
你就不能敷衍他一下吗
Can we eat now?
可以吃面了吗
Go ahead.
可以了
Eat up.
吃吧吃吧
Oh,
对了
these noodles really need
我跟你们说这个面呢
vinegar to taste good.
一定要放醋才好吃
Here, pour some on.
来 都倒上
I don't like vinegar.
我不吃醋
Just eat.
赶紧吃吧你
You're lucky to have food.
有的吃不错了
Exactly.
就是
Captain.
队长
Thank you.
谢谢
9521?
九五二一
Feng Sir!
冯科长
What are you doing here?
你在这儿干什么
I'm asking you,
我问你话呢
Checking records.
查资料
Who allowed you in?
谁让你进来的
You should be
你现在应该
patrolling the streets right now.
在大街上巡逻
What are you doing checking records here?
你在这儿查什么资料
Speak up!
说话
It was Officer Wang.
王警官
He asked me to write
是王警官让我写
a summary report for this month's work.
本月的工作总结报告
Wang Yong!
王永
Feng Sir.
科长
Is that true?
是这么回事儿吗
Yes, it is.
是这么回事儿
I thought
我看他上次
his last meeting notes
写的会议记录
were well done,
还不错
so I gave him some more tasks.
就给他找点儿事儿做
You arranged this?
你给他安排的
Yes.
是
How come I wasn't informed?
我怎么不知道
You weren't here.
您不在
Get lost!
滚
Yes Sir.
是
Chen Hao,
陈浩
this isn't like your
这不是你四所
Fourth Station archives
那个档案室
where you could come and go as you pleased.
你想进就进
Feng Sir,
冯科长
I really didn't know
我确实不知道
there were additional rules
进档案室
for entering the archives.
还有什么别的规矩
Did I miss
我是不是漏了
some other procedure?
什么别的手续
You're here to look up previous cases?
你来查之前的案子啊
Which case?
查的什么案子
The Miss Wang burglary case.
王小姐失窃案
Then why are you looking
那你为什么会在这儿
in the vehicle records cabinet?
查车辆档案柜
It's my first visit.
我第一次进来
I wasn't clear on the layout.
不太能搞得清楚位置
Then you better
那你就搞清楚
know your place.
自己的位置
Understood.
知道了
Listen up,
你给我听好了
from today onwards,
从今天开始
if you want to access the archives,
你想进档案室
you must apply through me.
必须跟我申请
I have to
我同意
approve it first.
你才能进
Yes, Sir!
是
Get out.
出去
Hi.
哥
As usual.
老样子
Okay.
好
Take care.
慢走啊
Everything alright?
没事儿吧
All good.
没事儿
Boss, boss.
大哥 大哥
With so many guards at the door,
门口这么多人看守
Mr. Peng is probably detained inside.
估计彭记者就关在里面
We should leave.
先走吧
Today, we went to
我们今天去了
the address registered for the truck.
货车登记的地址
The building was heavily guarded,
楼里楼外都是人
so we speculate
我们推测
that Mr. Peng
彭记者应该
is likely held inside,
就被关在里面
which is why we're considering taking a risk.
所以想冒险试一试
However, Xiang Yuansheng and I
但是我和向远生的
need
计划里
another hand for our plan,
还缺少一个帮手
so I wanted to ask
所以想向你请示一下
if Luo Minmin
能不能让骆珉敏
could join us.
参与这次行动
The former female officer from the Fourth Station?
以前四所那名女警员
Yes, you remember?
对 你还有印象
Of course,
当然
I have a deep impression.
印象还很深呢
She saved Li Qiushi.
她救过黎秋实
When Mrs. Peng
当初彭太太
first came to report at the Fourth Station,
来四所报案的时候
she was the officer who took the call.
就是她接的警
She's been involved from the start
她从一开始就卷了进来
and now she wants to see the investigation through
她现在想有始有终地
to the end.
查完彭记者失踪案
What reason do I have
那我还有什么理由
to refuse?
拒绝呢
Great,
好
I'll inform her
我马上把这个消息
right away.
告诉她
Stay safe.
务必注意安全
Am I late?
我来晚了吗
Come over, we're planning right now.
过来 正在商量计划
Here's the route for tomorrow.
这是明天的路线
Minmin,
珉敏
can you read the map now?
你现在能认得地图吗
Yes.
能
When she first came to the Fourth Station
她刚来四所的时候
she couldn't even tell north from south.
连东南西北都分不清
Captain,
队长
I've seriously memorized the Shanghai map
这次我在女警训练班
at the female police training class.
认真记了上海地图
No matter where you drop me,
不管把我扔在哪里
I can find my way back.
我都能找到回去的路
I'm the squad leader
我在我们女警训练班
at our training class.
是班长
Looks like you can handle things on your own now.
看来可以独当一面了
But tomorrow
但是明天
will be your first field operation.
是你第一次行动
You must follow Xiang Yuansheng's lead,
一切都要听向远生的
understood?
明白吗
Understood.
明白
Don't worry,
放心
I'll take good care of her.
我会照顾好她
Good.
好
Alright, let's assign the tasks.
来 分配任务
Since they're looking for Mrs. Peng,
既然他们想找彭太太
we'll lead them into our trap.
那我们就将计就计
Captain Chen.
陈队长
What are you up to?
干吗呢
Captain Wang,
王队长
just keeping an eye on this rickshaw
帮人车夫看着车呢
while the driver's gone to the bathroom.
人上厕所去了
Getting tired
这就累了
and slacking off, huh?
偷懒吧
No.
没
Any instructions?
有什么指示吗
No instructions.
没指示
Get in!
上车
Police work.
警察办案
You stay here.
你在这儿守着
Stay alert. I'm going to inform Feng Sir.
看好了 我去通知科长
He must be going to notify Feng Guangyun.
他应该去通知冯广云了
There are still people at the door.
门口还有人
Now, hurry and through the window.
你趁现在 赶紧翻窗走
Here.
来
I'm not cold.
我不冷
These are navy sailor gloves.
这是海军水兵的手套
For preventing blisters.
防磨手的
They'll probably
他们应该
be after us soon.
很快就追过来了
You sure you won't come with me?
你真的不一起走吗
If Feng Guangyun comes
冯广云如果来了
and doesn't see me here,
没看到我
he'll get suspicious.
肯定会起疑
I need to buy Chen Hao
我得尽量给陈浩
as much time as possible.
争取更多的时间
Be careful.
你自己小心
Watch your head.
小心头
Slowly.
慢点儿
You saw her go in?
你看着她进去的
Yes, Sir.
是的
Did you get a good look at the woman's face?
看清楚那女的长相了吗
Clear as day.
看得清清的
She's wearing
她穿的衣服
the same clothes
跟那个记者老婆的
as the journalist's wife.
一模一样
It's definitely her.
就是她
Stay at the door, don't alarm her.
守在门口别惊动她
I'm on my way.
我马上到
Bring your team
带上你的人
and head to No. 23 Wangyun Road immediately.
马上去望云路二十三号
I'm pulling back the Criminal Investigation Dept. officers.
我把刑警科的人撤走
Take action when you arrive.
你们到了直接动手
Hurry up and draw a card.
快点儿抓牌 快点儿
What are you dawdling for?
磨叽什么
Play that one.
打那个
You,
老五
come with me to the bathroom, quick.
陪我拉个屎 快
You need company to use the bathroom?
你拉个屎要我陪
Go by yourself!
你自个儿去
You're just sitting there
你搁那儿卖单呢
not playing, come on!
又不打 快
Why do you
你让我上
need me to come with you?
陪着干吗呀
Oh, right,
对对对
take the key.
快给我拿钥匙
It's pinching me.
硌屁股
I can't believe you...
我说你这人真的是
you...
你
you sure know how to take a shit.
你放这玩意儿真快啊你
You've made me want to take a dump, too.
我被你弄得我都想拉了
Give me some paper!
你给我点儿纸
No, no, no!
别别别
Leave me some!
你都给我拿走
Am I supposed to use my hands?
我拿手 手抠啊
Use your hands then!
你抠你的去啊你
Who did it? It stinks!
谁做的事啊这么臭
Hey,
老五
be careful not to drop the keys.
小心钥匙别掉坑里啊
I asked you to accompany me
我让你来陪我拉个屎
and now you're all worked up.
你倒来上劲了
Sounds like you're straining.
听你这声还挺费劲呢
Fine, I'm not waiting for you.
行 那我不等你了
I'm heading back.
我回去了啊
Play your card, come on!
你打啊 快点儿
Don't rush me.
别催啊
Hurry up!
快点儿 快
Always so slow.
每次打牌都这么慢
Nine bam!
九万
Think twice
这不得看清楚打啊
Peng!
彭记者
Peng Ganwen!
彭甘文
South wind!
南风
Yes!
碰
I won!
胡了
Really?
真的假的
Stop dawdling, play!
磨叽啥呢 出牌啊
This round is mine!
这把我能赢
Come on, play your card!
快呀 快出牌吧
You want it?
你要啊
Take or drop?
要不要
Stop dawdling.
别磨叽了
Shuffle up.
洗牌
Let's go.
来来来
Satisfied?
这行了吧
That works. It's actually quite good.
这可以 这个还挺好
A big hand, right?
凑成一把大的 是吧
Mr. Feng,
冯哥
they've been inside the room
人在房间里面
and haven't come out.
一直没出来
The same room as before?
还是之前那个房间
Yes.
是
Man guarding the door?
门口派人守着了
Take him back to the station.
你带他回分局吧
You don't need to handle this here anymore.
这儿不用你们管了
Okay.
好
That journalist's wife
那个记者的老婆
is in that room,
就在这个房间
and so is Xiang Yuansheng.
向远生也在
He might be armed,
他很有可能有武器
so be careful.
都小心点儿
Our target is that woman.
我们的目标是那个女人
Understood!
是
You guys, go in!
你们几个 上
Mr. Feng.
冯哥
The room down the corridor?
最里面那间
Yes.
是
Give me the money!
给钱
Get some water!
拿水
Water!
水
The door won't open!
门打不开
Move aside! Water's coming!
闪开闪开 水来了
Peng!
彭记者
Where's the water?
水呢
Mr. Feng, no one inside.
冯哥 里边没人
They must have jumped out the window.
应该跳窗走的
Of course!
废话
You think I didn't know?
这还用你说
Go find them!
去找人啊
Understood!
是
Let's go.
走
Wait a second.
等会儿
What is it, Mr. Feng?
怎么了冯哥
How many men are guarding the journalist?
记者那儿留了几个人
Seven.
七个
Call and check on them now!
赶紧打电话确认情况
Yes!
是
Stop!
站住
Don't run!
别跑
Quick!
快
Halt!
站住
Stop right there! Stop!
别跑 站住
Come back here!
别跑